[{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679176361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":43257,"timeElapsed":389940},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679185463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":399043},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7852,"timeElapsed":406899},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5354,"timeElapsed":412259},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5106,"timeElapsed":417369},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679208234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4439,"timeElapsed":421813},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679210373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":423952},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679214851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4474,"timeElapsed":428430},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":15915,"timeElapsed":444351},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679239070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6860,"timeElapsed":452650},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679245440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6365,"timeElapsed":459019},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679248038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2594,"timeElapsed":461618},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2179,"timeElapsed":463801},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2564,"timeElapsed":466369},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3129,"timeElapsed":469502},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679260064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4138,"timeElapsed":473644},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679263117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3048,"timeElapsed":476696},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679267053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3932,"timeElapsed":480633},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679279221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6323,"timeElapsed":492801},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679281431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2205,"timeElapsed":495010},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1795,"timeElapsed":496809},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679285031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1797,"timeElapsed":498611},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2214,"timeElapsed":500829},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2425,"timeElapsed":503258},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679292574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2890,"timeElapsed":506153},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679296235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3656,"timeElapsed":509815},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2337,"timeElapsed":512156},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679327535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":12979,"timeElapsed":541115},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679329985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2444,"timeElapsed":543564},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679333053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3064,"timeElapsed":546633},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679335443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":549022},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679338742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":552322},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679341612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2865,"timeElapsed":555192},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679343999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":557578},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679347627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3624,"timeElapsed":561206},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679350260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2630,"timeElapsed":563840},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679492268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":140556,"timeElapsed":705847},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679495428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":709008},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679503451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8017,"timeElapsed":717030},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679507747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4291,"timeElapsed":721326},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679517090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":9340,"timeElapsed":730670},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679519405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":732985},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679523874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4465,"timeElapsed":737454},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679526879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3000,"timeElapsed":740458},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679530910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4027,"timeElapsed":744490},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679541540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9091,"timeElapsed":755119},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679543603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":757183},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679545390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":758969},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679547880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":761459},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679552511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4628,"timeElapsed":766091},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679555415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2900,"timeElapsed":768995},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679558027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2608,"timeElapsed":771606},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679560788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2758,"timeElapsed":774368},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679563585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2792,"timeElapsed":777164},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679570930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5662,"timeElapsed":784510},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679572582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":786162},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679574695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2109,"timeElapsed":788275},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679579665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4966,"timeElapsed":793245},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679587116,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7446,"timeElapsed":800695},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679594733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7613,"timeElapsed":808313},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679598200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3462,"timeElapsed":811779},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679601443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3240,"timeElapsed":815023},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679605169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3722,"timeElapsed":818749},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679609045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3872,"timeElapsed":822625},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679629071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":18874,"timeElapsed":842651},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679630814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":844394},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679645216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":14397,"timeElapsed":858795},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679647453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2234,"timeElapsed":861033},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679650624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":864204},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679652901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2273,"timeElapsed":866481},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679677083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":24178,"timeElapsed":890663},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679786855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":109768,"timeElapsed":1000435},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679789011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":1002591},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679798601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5413,"timeElapsed":1012181},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679802238,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3633,"timeElapsed":1015818},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679807787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5544,"timeElapsed":1021367},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679941726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":133935,"timeElapsed":1155306},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679944617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2887,"timeElapsed":1158197},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679947150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":1160730},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679949079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1925,"timeElapsed":1162659},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679951140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2056,"timeElapsed":1164720},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679953986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":1167565},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679956070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2081,"timeElapsed":1169650},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679963857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":6565,"timeElapsed":1177437},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680043628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":79767,"timeElapsed":1257208},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680045863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2231,"timeElapsed":1259443},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680048484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2617,"timeElapsed":1262064},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680054257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5769,"timeElapsed":1267837},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680056032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1771,"timeElapsed":1269612},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680058700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2665,"timeElapsed":1272280},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680063354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4649,"timeElapsed":1276934},{"subjectID":"ut3o8bm77b","prolificID":"6732dd2ad292849faaca9cd3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b36d2808b62a6046295","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680099278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":35920,"timeElapsed":1312858}]